# Leandro dos Anjos Tavares

leandroanjostavares@gmail.com

+55 11976910592

São Paulo / Brazil Willing to relocate

## Key skills

- Problem-Solving
- Collaborative Team Player
- Adaptability
- Self-motivated
- Typescript
- Angular
- Java
- Spring Boot
- Git
- Node
- Back-end
- Front-end

## **Education**

Bachelor degree in Information Systems

Universidade Paulista -UNIP - São Paulo, SP

# **Summary**

I'm a self-motivated and collaborative software developer with over 7 years of experience, 5 of these in the banking sector with several languages and I'm interested in learning more every day. Even though I work both backend and front-end, I am fascinated with the front-end. I'm moving to New Zealand and I'm looking for a job as a software developer.

## **Career history**

## Senior Software Engineer at Itaú Bank

June 2022 to Present

Focused on front-end projects, we created an internal micro front end platform that aggregated services from other areas and migrated legacy projects to the new cloud architecture and technologies. I also train new devs to improve skills in front-end technologies.

Achievements: I helped a deaf person to become a front-end software developer

#### **Intermediate Systems Analyst** at Original Bank

March 2018 to June 2022

Analyzing and developing new tools for the company's internal and external systems contacting customers and using Java 6 and 8+ (Spring Boot), Angular (JS and 4+), SQL Databases and legacy technologies.

#### Full Stack Developer at Clapme

October 2016 to March 2018

Maintenance and creation of new tools (front and back) on the company's websites using Ruby on Rails, html, css, sass, javascript, jquery. Studying and developing multiplatforms Apps, Android and IOS using React-Native and Ionic.

# **Additional Information**

Undergraduate thesis - Adhesion of Cobit 5 framework in relation to information security rule ABNT NBR ISO/IEC 27002:2013

Published in SENAC Scientific Initiation Magazine Vol. 5 no 4 year 2015 link. (portuguese)

http://www1.sp.senac.br/hotsites/blogs/revistainiciacao/index.php/vol-5-4-ano-2016/